The lamp oil
has been tampered with.
Vice Director Shen,
the Director summons you.
Coming.
Director.
Vice Director Shen,
did you rest well last night?
That oil lamp
was specially prepared for you.
It has a calming effect.
Thank you for your kindness, Director.
For today's morning lesson,
I will explain the affairs within the tower to you.
Yes,
Director.
This is the Ziwei Hall,
where heaven and earth reside.
This person
is imitating my father.
You are very knowledgeable, Director.
I have learned a lot.
This token allows access to the first to third floors of the Black Tower.
Since you are the Vice Director,
you should familiarize yourself with the affairs in the tower.
Thank you, Director.
Is this
the Blood Pool?
No.
This is the Dragon Marrow Pool,
brewed with ninety-nine rare medicinal herbs
to nourish the foundation of the dragon vein.
The dragon vein is deep at the bottom of the pool.
New medicine needs to be added every seven days.
Everything is for His Majesty
and for the foundation of Tianqi.
It's dangerous near the pool.
Please stop here, Vice Director Shen.
It's alright.
You are a sensible man, Vice Director Shen.
Your father, Shen Qingshan,
also stood here back then
and strongly agreed with this great cause.
Where is my father
now?
He is down there.
The core of the dragon vein needs someone with a pure Yang destiny to guard it.
Your father
went down voluntarily.
I'm sorry, My Lord.
I didn't mean to.
Drag him away.
The liquid in the Blood Pool contains sedatives.
The Taoists are controlled by the drugs.
The old servant stole blood crystal powder to write a warning.
This person must be very close to my father.
This stone slab is very hard.
To be able to leave marks,
requires a lot of strength.
A servant suddenly fell ill last night.
The Director has ordered someone to bury him.
You don't need to worry, Vice Director Shen.
Calming.
Bewitching.
Mo'er,
why haven't you come to save me yet?
You are right here in the tower,
but you only care about saving yourself.
Illusion.
There's indeed something wrong with the lamp oil.
The sweet-scented base
has the same origin as the liquid in the Blood Pool.
With the addition of Datura flowers,
the extract causes hallucinations.
The purple sparks suggest
that mineral powder was mixed in.
Heat activates the medicinal properties.
That oil lamp
was specially prepared for you.
It has a calming effect.